 [
    {
      "question": "A Word Can Destroy Me",
      "answer": "Silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has keys but can't open locks?",
      "answer": "A piano"
    },
    {
      "question": "What travels around the world while staying in a corner?",
      "answer": "A stamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "What comes up but never comes down?",
      "answer": "Your age"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has a head and a tail but no body?",
      "answer": "A coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "I Can Fill A Room Or Just One Heart",
      "answer": "Loneliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "I FEEL YOUR EVERY MOVE. I KNOW YOUR EVERY THOUGHT. I’M WITH YOU FROM BIRTH AND I’LL SEE YOU WHEN YOU ROT",
      "answer": "Your reflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can you break, even when you never pick it up or touch it?",
      "answer": "A promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "No Man Can Hold It",
      "answer": "Your breath"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is yours but mostly used by others?",
      "answer": "Your name"
    },
    {
      "question": "When I Reveal Myself, You Will Never Be The Same?",
      "answer": "Betrayal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of lion never roars?",
      "answer": "A dandelion"
    },
    {
      "question":
        "What’s bright orange with green on top and sounds like a parrot?",
      "answer": "A carrot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s really easy to get into, and hard to get out of?",
      "answer": "Trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "TWEEDLEDUM AND TWEEDLEDEE SAW IT, CAN YOU SEE IT",
      "answer": "Seesaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "WHAT IS ALWAYS ON ITS WAY HERE BUT NEVER ARRIVES??",
      "answer": "Tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "WITHOUT FINGERS I POINT, WITHOUT ARMS I STRIKE, WITHOUT FEET I RUN. WHAT AM I",
      "answer": "A clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "MY GREATEST OF MY STRENGTHS IS THAT I KNOW MY WORTH. I HUG MYSELF SO TIGHTLY AT EVERY BIRTH",
      "answer": "A knot"
    },
    {
      "question":
        "You cut me, slice me, dice me, and all the while, you cry. What am I?",
      "answer": "An Onion"
    }
  ]